他们死了
They're dead.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
（忆往昔）
我不是想招募你
I'm not trying to recruit you,
但你需要知道 情况在变化
but you need to know, things are changing.
你正好赶上任务报告
You're just in time for the briefing.
我是说 如果你想听听
I mean, that is if you wanna hear.
我们打算怎么清除全美境内所有的吸血鬼
how we're gonna exterminate every last vampire in America.
你总是中立
You're always playing the middle.
这一次 你能不能选个立场
For once, why don't you pick a side?
地狱猎犬
The hellhounds.
把灵魂出卖给恶魔后
See, when you sell your soul to a demon,
它们就会来把你的灵魂扯出来
they're the one that come and rip it out of you.
- 别动 - 你能控制它们
- Stay! - You can control them?!
把你弄到这儿来
Getting you here…
我修改了咒语
…I managed to pervert that spell.
让你的灵体没有被送回笼子
so your essence wasn't sent back to the Cage.
你觉得这事会怎样结局
How do you think this is going to end?
你被打败时 会措手不及
You're not even gonna see it comin' when you get taken down.
- 就凭你 - 还有我的骨血
- By you? - And my flesh and blood.
你记得凯莉·克莱恩吗
You remember Kelly Kline?
那不是个孩子 那是路西法的后代
This is not a baby. This is the spawn of Lucifer.
凯莉 天使 他们都想要你死
Kelly, the angels? They want you dead.
但我可以保护你
But I can protect you.
- 我都不知道你的名字呢 - 大衮
- I don't even know your name. - Dagon.
始祖吸血鬼死了
The Alpha Vampire is dead.
你们在改变世界 我想加入进来
You're changing the world, and I wanna be a part of it.
- 我加入 - 你哥哥呢
- I'm in. - And your brother?
给我点时间
Give me some time.
（如今）
（内布拉斯加州 谢里敦县）
天呐
Oh, my God.
亲爱的 我们需要更多柴火
Babe, we're gonna need more wood.
好吧 但首先 来看看这视频
Okay, but first, check out this video.
这熊冲这些人发疯了
This bear goes crazy on these guys, and he j…
不 我们出来不是为了看视频的
Um, no. That's not why we come out here.
我们是来跟大自然沟通的
We come out here to commune with nature,
不是来看人被大自然吞噬的
not watch people get eaten by it.
好吧 首先
Okay, first of all…
它没吃了他们
…he … he doesn't eat them.
它把他们赶上了一棵树 他们哭了
He chases them up a tree, and they cry.
哭得很惨
A lot.
它想干吗
What do they want?!
- 超搞笑的 - 天呐 拜托
- It's hilarious. - Oh, my God. Please …
其次 「跟大自然沟通」
And second of all, "commune with nature"?
我以为你带我出来
I thought you brought me out here.
是为了脱光光 干奇怪的事
to get naked and do weird stuff.
不会那么奇怪的
Yeah, it's not gonna get that weird.
我会想念这样的
I'll miss this.
我会想念你的
I'll miss you.
我明白
And I get it.
华盛顿有
I mean, Washington has.
最棒的兽医培训项目
the best veterinary program in the country.
你考进了 你必须去
You got in. I mean, you have to go.
但异地恋也有很多成功案例 是吧
But people make this long distance thing work all the time, right?
是啊 当然
Right. Sure.
我再去弄点柴火来
I'm gonna get more firewood.
好
Okay.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
男人点 她会答应的
Just man up. She'll say yes.
格温 快跑
Gwen! Run!
马库斯
Marcus?
天呐
Oh, my God!
[邪恶力量 第12季第15集]
接二连三 真是可以载入史册
Back to back to back. That was one for the books.
- 是啊 - 天呐
- Yeah. - Man!
老爸会喜欢这玩意的
Dad loved this thing.
哥们 那个…
Dude, on the … on the …
别别…
No, don't, don't, don't, don't!
- 别坐 - 怎么了
- Don't s - What?
迪恩 你一身食尸鬼 还有死灵残骸
Dean, you're covered in ghoul, man, and … and … and wraith.
你…
You…
你头发里还有一点海妖残骸
you have a piece of siren in your hair.
恶心
Gross.
是啊
Yeah.
哥们 你去冲个澡
Dude, why don't you take a shower.
换件衣服吧
and change your clothes?
你那内裤穿四天了
You've been wearing the same pair of boxers for four days.
好吧 首先
Okay, one,
你知道我带了几条内裤也太怪了
weird that you know how much underwear I packed.
- 你就觉得这点怪 - 其次 是两天加两天
- That's what's weird about this? - And B, it's two and two.
翻过来穿不算同一条
Doesn't count if you flip 'em inside out.
（弗罗多 内布拉斯加州 谢里敦县 失踪宿营者 现场一片狼藉）
又来案子了
Got another case.
不是吧 这么快 你怎么做到的
Really? Already? How'd you do that?
跟其他的一样
Same as the others.
我做了个算法 筛选警用频道
I-I made a computer algorithm that scrapes data from police scanners,
求救电话 本地新闻网站的数据
emergency calls, uh, local news sites,
然后对一切进行…
and then it puts everything through a h…
电脑告诉我的
The computer told me.
电脑啊
Computers.
怪物 黄片
Monsters, porn.
它们还有什么做不到的吗
Is there anything they can't do?
好吧
All right.
- 那我们去吧 - 行
- Well, let's get to it, then. - Yeah, that's fine.
哥们 你先收拾一下的
And, dude, um… after you get cleaned up.
- 车里有湿巾 - 迪恩 我说真的
- I got baby wipes in the car. - Dude. Dean, I'm serious, man.
你一身尸臭味儿
You smell like roadkill.
因为累活儿都是我干的
That's 'cause I do all the heavy lifting.
- 你… - 好吧
- You - All right.
我要用你一直藏着不让我用的梦幻洗发水
I'm using that fancy shampoo you keep hidden from me.
是吗 太好了 妈妈
Oh, really? Oh, that's great, Mom.
- 不 我们没事 - 听上去挺有希望
- No, we're … we're fine. We, uh… - It sounds like somethin'.
- 嗯 我也爱你 - 好 小卡 再联络
- Yeah. Love you, too. - All right, Cass. Let us know.
- 好 再见 - 你先说
- All right, bye. - You first.
妈妈刚在亚克朗市摆平一只鬼
Mom just finished working a haunting in Akron.
- 英国人吗 - 嗯
- The Brits? - Yeah.
真好 找谁呢 混蛋捉鬼队
Great. Who you gonna call? Douchebusters.
- 你呢 - 是小卡
- What about you? - That was Cass.
他在爱达荷州科达伦 又有人在杀天使了
He's in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho. Someone's killing angels. Again.
（餐厅服务员莎拉·达申斯基英年早逝 惨死在一个暴脾气外星人手下 餐厅经理赫伯·尼尔森如是说）
好吧 听上去不错 我这就给您拿水
All right, sounds good. I'll get your waters right away.
你好 可以跟你们经理谈谈吗
Hello. I'd like to speak to your manager, if I could.
我是赫伯·尼尔森 这里的老板
I'm, uh, Herb Nelson. I run this joint.
幸会
Pleasure to meet you,
索兰奇探员
Agent…Solange.
我来是为了…
I'm, uh, I'm here about…
我知道你为什么来
Oh, I-I-I know why you're here.
跟我来
Follow me.
悄悄的
Quietly.
这是什么
What is this?
这个嘛…
Well…
你也知道
You know…
小心驶得万年船
Can't be too careful.
他们总在监视 窃听
They're always watching, listening.
是吗
They are?
是啊 但这里是安全的
Oh, yeah. But we're safe in here.
钢筋钢
Reinforced steel.
谁都别想进来
Nothing's gettin' through this sucker.
是啊
Yeah.
你是为了莎拉来的
So, uh, you're here about Sara.
对 你的服务员
Yes, your waitress.
在这篇文章中 你说
In this article, you said, uh,
你说她是被一个外星人杀死的
you said that she was killed by an alien.
不是普通的外星人 爬行生物
Well, not just aliens. Reptilians.
就像英国女王
You know… like the Queen of England.
好吧
Right.
这大有帮助 谢谢你的配合
Okay, well, that's very helpful. Thank you so much for your time.
我有证据
And I-I got proof.
那个
You know…
看
See?
大部分普通人受不了真相
Most sheeple can't handle the truth.
但我行 我是清醒的
But not me. I'm woke.
所以
It's, uh…
我不用新技术
…why I don't use, uh, new tech.
96年之后的东西 都是陷阱
Anything past '96, it's a trap.
掌上电脑
You know…Palm Pilot.
追踪设备还差不多 是吧
It's more like Tracking Device. Am I right?
嗯
Right.
是啊
Exactly.
看好了
Now watch this.
好了
Now, here we go.
我不知道她是谁
Okay, now I-I don't know who she is.
可能也是个外星人
Probably another alien.
她怀孕了 我赌是产仔皇后
She's preggers, so my money's on brood queen.
我也不知道他是谁
Now, I don't know who he is either.
瞧 那是莎拉
There! That's Sara.
看 银刀
Look, look, look. See? Silver knives.
那是外星金属
That's, uh, star metal.
嗯 摄像头被烧坏了
Yeah, the … the camera got fried.
但你看到了吧
But you… you saw it, yeah?
就在…
R-right…
这里
…there.
- 她有 - 黄眼睛
- She has… - Yellow eyes.
就像我说的 是爬行生物
Like I said … reptilian.
本地警察 他们
Now the local cops, they…
他们以为是…他们不相信我
they think there's something … you know, they don't believe me.
他们以为是摄像头有问题
They think there's something weird with the camera.
但…所以你才来了
But, I mean, that's why you're here.
联调局 黑衣人
The … the FBI Man in Black.
米色衣
Well, you know, beige.
要我说 是被熊抓了
You ask me, a bear got him.
可能是美洲狮
Maybe a cougar.
这里有一滩血 那里还有
Found a fair amount of blood over here and some there,
没有尸体
but no body.
可能行凶的东西把他拖走了
Figure whatever did this dragged him off.
除非你们打算
So unless you guys are lookin' to.
对动物立案
make a Federal case on some critters…
长官 你说有个生还者
Sir, you said there was a survivor.
对 格温·赫南德兹
Yeah. Gwen Hernandez.
但她吓得不轻
Uh, but she's pretty shaken up,
说了好多奇怪的话
saying all sorts of strange things.
比如呢
Like what?
比如 他们是被狼袭击的
Like that they were attacked by a wolf …
隐形的狼
an invisible wolf.
姑娘说 那玩意突然冒出来
Girl says that, you know, it came outta nowhere.
还想袭击她
and that it's coming after her next.
少来了
Right.
治安官 谢谢你
Sheriff, thank you.
隐形狗
Invisible dog, huh?
听上去像地狱猎犬
Sounds like a hellhound to me.
是啊
Yeah.
格温 快跑
Gwen! Run!
马库斯
Marcus?
天呐
Oh, my God!
这太蠢了 是个蠢主意
This is dumb. It's a dumb idea.
格温看到什么东西杀了她男友
Listen, Gwen saw something kill her boyfriend.
还觉得它接下来想袭击她
and she thinks it's coming for her next.
- 我们得告诉她 - 告诉她什么
- We just gotta tell her - Tell her what?
真的 萨姆 你打算说什么
No, seriously, Sam, what are you gonna say?
「你好 我是萨姆·温彻斯特
"Hi, my name is Sam Winchester.
这是比我帅得多的哥哥 迪恩 我们猎魔
This is my much handsomer brother Dean. We hunt monsters.
你搞的那个男的
Oh, and that guy you were banging?
他应该是跟一个恶魔做了交易
We're pretty sure he made a deal with a demon,
所以地狱猎犬跑来把他的灵魂拖入地狱了
So a hellhound came and dragged his soul to Hell.
但你呢 你没事
But you? You're cool.
既然这里没有东西需要我们杀了 我们走了「
And since there's nothing around for us to kill, peace out."
说完了吗
You done?
嗯 我们不那么说 迪恩
Yeah, we don't say that, Dean.
我们得说点能让她获得安宁
We say something that'll give her peace.
- 让她晚上能入睡的话 - 那就撒谎呗
- You know, help her sleep at night. - Oh, so we lie?
对 弥天大谎
Yeah, a lot.
格温·赫南德兹
Gwen Hernandez?
联调局贝克和克莱普顿探员 可以进去吗
Agents Baker and Clapton. FBI. May we come in?
- 我不… - 我们只想谈谈
- I…I don't want any… - We just wanna talk.
就是谈谈马库斯的事
That's all. About Marcus.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 你们坐吧 - 好
- You can have a seat. - Right.
格温 我们今天来是因为
Gwen, uh, we're here today because we, uh,
我们知道你对警察说了什么
we know what you told the police,
你觉得好像有
that you feel like something…
超自然的东西要伤害你
supernatural is after you.
但我们已经结束了调查
But we've concluded our investigation,
杀死你男友的东西
and the thing that killed your boyfriend …
是只熊
Was a bear.
我们找到了它 也杀掉它了
Now we found it and put it down.
你已经没有危险了 好吗
So you're no longer in any kind of danger, okay?
我不…
I don't…
我知道我看到了什么
I-I know what I saw.
格温 你经历创伤时
Gwen, when you go through a traumatic experience,
有时候你的大脑会编造记忆
sometimes your mind can make things up.
- 出去 - 什么
- Get out. - Sorry?
滚出我家
Get out of my house.
好吧 冷静 我们只是想帮忙
Okay, calm down. We're just trying to help.
我不需要你们帮忙
I don't need your help.
我知道我看到了什么
I know what I saw.
- 格温 - 出去
- Gwen… - Get out!
好吧
Okay.
嗯 她会睡得香又甜的
Oh, yeah. She's gonna sleep like a baby.
没事 你不会有事的 好吗
It's okay. You're gonna be okay. All right?
肯定让你很不爽吧
It must really burn you,
知道是我把你关进了这座监狱
knowing I'm the one who put you in this prison.
我
Me.
你是我的
I own you,
我为我们做了很多计划
and I have big plans for us.
我好荣幸
I'm flattered.
如此费心
All this hard work,
那么…
all that…
让他们颤抖 猛汉
You get 'em, slugger!
我还是要剥了你的皮 吃了你的灵魂
I'm still gonna peel off your skin and eat your soul.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Is that so? - Yeah.
会弄得比较…乱
I mean, it will be… little bit messy,
但是
But…
总得维护名声嘛 你理解的
You know, gotta protect the rep. You understand.
我理解 但就凭你 还铐着那锁链
I do. But you, in … in those chains?
原谅我没有吓得发抖
I mean, forgive me if I'm not quaking in my Testonis.
我觉得我们都明白 这
Oh, I think both you and I understand that this?
只是暂时的
It's just a temporary situation.
是吗
Oh, do we?
我明白
See, I understand.
不管你有什么可悲的小阴谋
that whatever sad little scheme that you're brewing up,
我都先你十步了
I'm already 10 steps ahead.
我还以为自傲是我的罪孽呢
And I thought pride was my sin.
不是自傲 是事实
It's not pride. It's fact.
你惹我 我碾压你
You cross me, I crush you.
你打我 我用双倍力气奉还
You hit me, I hit you back twice as hard.
你让我做你的狗
You make me your dog,
我让你做我的奴
I make you my slave.
有人吗
Hello?
克劳力 陛下
Crowley. My lord.
陛下
My lord.
有人找
Duty calls.
别担心我 我就坐这儿
Don't worry about me. I'll just sit right here.
没错
Yes, you will.
重口
Kinky.
干什么
What?
抱歉 陛下 就是…
Apologies, Your Excellence. It's just, um…
周会您已经迟到一小时了
You're already an hour late for the weekly meeting.
上周我们就延迟了…
And we had to push last week, so…
您有410项十字路口交易
You have 410 crossroad deals.
需要高级管理层批准
that need senior management approval,
还有638件其他事宜
on top of the 638 other matters.
需要您马上处理
that require your immediate response.
好吧
Fine.
格温
Gwen, that, um,
那玩意 是只地狱猎犬
that thing was a hellhound.
什么
A…what?
地狱猎犬
Hellhound.
挺难解释的
Kind of hard to explain.
简单说 就是地狱的巨大隐形猎犬
Basically, giant, invisible hounds from Hell.
也不难嘛
Wasn't hard at all.
你们不是警察 是吧
So you guys are not cops, are you?
不 并不是
No. Not exactly.
我叫萨姆 他是我哥哥 迪恩
My name is Sam. That's my brother Dean.
我们猎魔
And we hunt monsters.
我们以前接触过地狱猎犬
And we've tangled with hellhounds in the past.
巫尘能挡住它们
Goofer dust'll keep 'em out.
恶魔刀或天使刃能杀死它们
A demon knife or an angel blade, that'll kill 'em.
等等
Wait.
那你们为什么对我说马库斯是熊杀的
So why did you tell me that Marcus got killed by a bear?
为了让你好受点 是他的主意
Make you feel better. It was his idea.
听着 我知道这听上去很疯狂
Listen, I know this sounds insane …
是啊
It does.
但是 我说了 我知道我看到了什么
But…like I said, I know what I saw.
我看到的就是疯狂的
And what I saw was insane.
是啊
Right.
这有点尴尬 但是
Now this is awkward, but, um…
地狱猎犬只会来抓把灵魂卖给了
hellhounds only come after people who sold their souls…
恶魔的人
to a demon.
那么10年前 你有没有特别想要什么
So about 10 years ago, did you really want something?
比如…凯蒂猫背包
Like…I don't know, a Hello Kitty backpack.
或者宿敌死去
or the death of an enemy?
没有
No.
马库斯呢 他有…
What about Marcus? Did he… Would he …
不会
No.
太好了 那怎么回事
Great. So what the hell?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我知道该问谁
But I do know who we can ask.
接下来 41号案件 阿瓦 一个三级恶魔
And moving on to, um, case 41, Awar, a Rank Three demon,
称他抓了六个孩子
claims to have had six babies.
但莫莱克斯 一个二级恶魔
But then Morax, a Rank Two demon,
夺走了他两个孩子 阿瓦就只剩…
took two of his babies, which would leave Awar with…
是的 四个孩子
yes, um, four babies.
我觉得我们都可以认同 这数目
Which I think we can all agree, isn't enough babies…
完全不够好好吃一顿
for a decent meal.
是啊 阿瓦寻求赔偿
No, not at all. Um, Awar is looking for compensation.
- 形式是 - 我不在乎
- in the form of - I don't care.
继续
Moving on.
我也是 继续说42号案件
Me either. Uh, moving on to case 42.
这个挺好 是关于侵权法改革的
This is a good one. It's on tort reform.
嗯
Yeah.
（不是小鹿 来电）
你有什么事
What the hell do you want?
好了 桃子 我知道你还在气
All right, Peaches, I get that you're still upset about.
- 那件… - 气
- the whole, uh… - Upset?
不 我已经完全忘了你和你们那群怪胎
No, I'm totally over how you and your little band of misfits.
送我儿子回到过去等死的事
sent my son back in time… to die!
好了 那是加文的决定
Okay, look, that was totally Gavin's call.
好吗 我们这里有点状况
All right? You know what? We have a situation here.
那么…再见
Oh, well, in that case…Bye.
地狱猎犬 克劳力
Hellhounds, Crowley.
你的一只恶犬在杀
One of your mutts is going after folks.
- 没有出卖灵魂的人 - 不可能
- who didn't sell their souls. - Not possible.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我的猎犬
My hounds…
有什么关于它们的事吗
You have anything to tell me?
那个…
Well…
我们…
We, uh…
本不想打扰您
didn't wanna bother you.
是拉姆齐
It was Ramsey.
它跑出去了 陛下
She got out, my lord.
处死犬舍守卫
Have the kennel guards killed.
死得痛苦点
Painfully.
我就…
I'll be right.
到
here.
想我了吗
You miss me?
适合外出的好天气
Nice day out.
你好 兄弟
Hello, brother.
凯文
Kelvin.
你还记得 我们只见过一次
Oh, you remember? We only met the once, so…
你在这儿做什么
What are you doing here?
跟你的目的一样
Same reason as you.
找凯莉·克莱恩
Track down Kelly Kline.
和她肚子里的那个魔鬼之子
and that unholy bun she's got in her oven.
我们互帮互助一下如何
So what do you say we help each other out?
你得明白
You have to understand,
这不是普通的地狱猎犬
this isn't just a hellhound.
是最厉害的地狱猎犬
This is the hellhound.
什么意思
That means what?
上帝说完「要有光」后
Right after God said, "Let there be light, "
他还创造了一堆其他东西
he … he made a whole bunch of things …
花束 考拉 地狱猎犬
posies, koalas, hellhounds.
他想要个造物主最好的朋友
He wanted The Creator's best friend,
但猎犬太凶残
but the hounds were too vicious.
所以他就打算把它们都杀掉
So he planned on having them all put down,
直到 我们最喜欢的坠落天使出现了
until along came our favorite fallen angel.
他救走了一只猎犬 一只怀孕的母狗 拉姆齐
He rescued one of the hounds … a pregnant bitch named Ramsey.
你为什么不能叫它乖乖听话
Why don't you just tell her to heel?
我控制不了它 没人能
I can't control her. No one can.
它只忠于路西法
She's loyal only to Lucifer.
等等 魔鬼吗
Wait, like the Devil?
对 但他关在笼子里呢
Yeah, but he's locked in a cage.
- 那就好 - 是啊
- Good.- Yeah.
好吧 那狗狗现在在哪呢
All right, so where is Fido now?
要我猜 应该是
Well, if I had to hazard a guess, I would say.
躲在哪个暖和舒适的窝里
huddled up in some nice, warm den.
它为什么要针对格温
Well, why is she after Gwen?
问她啊
Ask her.
我…
I…
我不…
I don't…
它袭击我们时 我还击了它
When it attacked us, I did hit it.
用斧子
With an ax.
这就对了 那母狗就喜欢记仇
Well, there you go. The bitch does tend to hold a grudge.
我们要么杀了拉姆齐
So we either kill Ramsey,
要么让猎犬吃了她
or the hound eats her.
有趣
Fun.
等等
Wait a second.
「我们」
"We"?
那样的狗狗到处乱跑会损害生意
Pup like that out and about is not good for business.
会让人们觉得我不能控制局面
Makes it look like I'm not in control.
但是 把那只狗的头挂在我的墙上
But that mutt's head mounted on my wall?
就是好广告了 是的 小鹿 我们一起行动
Good for the brand. So yes, Moose, for now, "We."
太好了 现在有只一心寻仇的地狱猎犬
Great. So we have a hellhound who's gunning for revenge,
还是私仇
and it's personal.
我还以为这行不会更奇怪了
Just when I thought this gig couldn't get any weirder…
总能更奇怪的
It can always get weirder.
我就知道
I knew it.
你们好
Hi, guys.
陛下
My lord…
我不配
I'm not worthy!
我们就知道克劳力在搞什么鬼
We knew Crowley was up to something.
他的那副表现
The way he's been acting?
而且他还杀了所有参与笼子项目的恶魔
And how he snuffed out everyone who was part of the Cage project?
我们很多人真的不喜欢克劳力
And a lot of us really don't like Crowley.
他太咋呼了
He's very prancy.
所以我们放了你的猎犬 分他的神
So we released your hound to create a distraction,
想看看他藏了什么
to see what he was hiding. ‭
- 我们 - 我们希望
- We - ‭We hoped …
我们知道肯定是你
We knew it could only be you.
我们带来了这个
And we brought this.
但是
But … but… ‭
我们放了你之前 我们有几件
Before we, uh, let you out, we have a few…
也不算是要求了
well, I wouldn't call them demands, exactly.
但是
But…
地狱猎犬人类看不到
So hellhounds are invisible to humans…
除非你卖了灵魂 它们来抓你
unless you sold your soul, and they're after you.
或是 戴上这个
Or, uh, you're wearing a pair of these.
这是用圣油炼过的眼镜
They're glasses treated with holy fire.
好了 克劳力和我进树林
All right, Crowley and I are gonna hit the woods,
看能不能找到魔犬
see if we can't track down Cujo.
你跟着萨姆 他会保护你
You stick with Sam. He'll keep you safe.
好
Okay.
照顾好她
Take care of her.
当然了
Of course.
迪恩 就算拉姆齐回来了
Dean, look, even if Ramsey circles back,
只要我们保持移动 格温就…
as long as we keep moving, Gwen's gonna be just…
你是指车
You're talking about the car.
- 你总是狠踩刹车 - 迪恩 我会开车
- You tend to ride the brakes. - Dean, I know how to drive.
我就是说说
I'm just saying.
把她想成
Okay, just imagine she's a…
一个美女
a beautiful woman.
- 不理你了 - 一个非常美丽的女人
- Come on. Get out of here. - A beautiful, beautiful woman.
- 受不了你 - 萨姆
- I'm done. - ‭Sam…
走吧
Come on.
（内布拉斯加州 谢里敦县 席卡谷）
天堂近况如何
So how are things in Heaven?
还算正常
Functional.
还是照常有内斗
You know, there's the usual infighting, but…
但是路西法要有孩子了
let's just say Lucifer having a baby on board has.
让我们团结了起来
brought us all together.
这是全员出动的情况 卡西迪奥
You know, this is an all hands on deck situation, Castiel.
包括你
Including yours.
你是来找我帮忙的吗
Okay, so you're here for my hands?
我们需要你
We want you.
你的外勤经验
Look, you got more field experience.
比一千个天使加起来都多
than the next thousand angels combined.
我觉得你高估我了
I think you overestimate me.
我没有
I don't.
我知道你在跟温家兄弟合作
Look, I know you're working with the Winchesters.
萨姆和迪恩
Sam and Dean.
他们的心意是好的 但是
their hearts are in the right place, but.
有我们做后援不是更好吗
wouldn't it be better to have us waiting in the proverbial wings?
有全天堂的力量支持你
All the power of Heaven behind you?
你会怀念吗 楼上的生活
You ever miss it? Upstairs?
别误会 我喜欢地球 很古怪
I mean, don't get me wrong. I love Earth. It's quirky.
一股干草味儿
It smells like hay.
但这里不是家 对吗
But it's not home, is it?
我不相信天堂欢迎我
I don't believe I'm welcome in Heaven.
没错
No, you're not.
他们还在记你的仇
They still hold a lot of grudges up there.
但如果我说 你可以回来呢
But what if I told you, you could come back?
你的一切罪孽都可以被忘记
That all your sins could be forgotten?
被原谅
Forgiven?
我会说你在撒谎
I would say that you're lying.
我没有
Oh, but I'm not.
你帮我们找到凯莉·克莱恩
You help us track down Kelly Kline,
天堂就欢迎你回去
and you will be welcomed back into the fold.
是嘛
Right.
你有权那么做
And you have the power to do that.
没有 我只是传个信儿
Oh, no, I can't. I'm just the messenger.
但约书亚有权
But Joshua can.
约书亚
Joshua.
我以为他让位了
I thought he stepped aside.
是的
He did.
但我说了 这是全员出动的情况
But like I said, all hands on deck situation.
想想看 卡西迪奥
Imagine it, Castiel …
可以随意来去
free to come and go as you please,
成为家庭一员
part of your family,
再次回归你真正的家庭
your true family, again.
听着
Look…
那位园丁有个计划
the Gardener's got a plan.
我们只求你听听我们说
All we ask is that you hear us,
听他说完
hear him out.
为了大局
For the greater good.
好了
All right. ‭
最后
and lastly…
你每年要给我一千个灵魂
You will grant me a thousand souls per year,
你要封我为
and you will anoint me…
新十字路口之王
the new King of the Crossroads.
太好了
Great. ‭
汤米 你还想要什么吗
Hey, Tommy, you want anything, man?
我唯一的心愿就是重振地狱
The only thing I care about is making Hell great again.
瞧
See?
什么
What?
好吧 我们来吧
All right. Let's do this.
好了 陛下
There we go, my lord.
我感觉好棒
I feel so good.
我们说好的
We had a deal!
是吗
Did we?
抱歉 孩子 你理解的吧
Sorry, kid. You understand, right?
不能留活口什么的
No … no witnesses or anything, yeah?
是的 杀了我吧 堕落者
Yes. Take me, oh, Fallen One!
我的生命随你吞噬
My life is yours to devour.
瞧 你这么一说就奇怪了
See, now you just made it weird.
真漂亮
Fancy.
很凸显你眼睛的魅力
Really bring out your eyes.
- 闭嘴 - 闭嘴
- Shut up. - Shut up.
- 我说真的 克劳力 - 我说真的 克劳力
- I mean it, Crowley. - I mean it, Crowley.
- 下地狱吧 - 下地狱吧
- Go to Hell. - ‭Go to Hell.
真的 迪恩 这么多年了 你太好猜了
Really, Dean, all these years, you're so predictable.
是啊 我们都变了
Yeah, well, I guess we've all changed.
我变得好猜了 你变心软了
I got predictable. You got soft.
几年前 谁能想到
I mean, a few years ago, who'd have thought.
你会帮我们救个姑娘
you'd be helping us save the girl of the week?
我才不在乎她
I don't care about her.
或许我们影响了你
Yeah, well, maybe we rubbed off on you.
少臭美了
Don't flatter yourself.
你救了小卡
You save Cass.
我就是不想看到温家男人伤春悲秋
Just to spare myself the Winchester Man Pain …
你俩像两个小女生一样哭哭啼啼
you lot moping about like a bunch of schoolgirls.
我想说 谢谢
I just wanna say thank you.
还有 几年前
Or…A few years ago,
谁能想到你会跟地狱之王合作
who would've thought you'd be working with the King of Hell?
或许是我影响了你
Maybe you've rubbed off on me.
或许 我的影响蹭了你一身
Maybe I've rubbed off all over you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
这事
This.
都怪我
It's all my fault.
- 格温 这不怪你 - 就怪我
- Gwen, this is not your fault. - Yes, it is.
马库斯的事
What happened to Marcus…
格温 快跑
Gwen! Run!
停车 求你
Pull over. Please.
好
Okay.
*我们去打猎*
*A hunting we will go*
克劳力 闭嘴 不开玩笑
Crowley, shut up. Seriously. ‭
拉姆齐把他拖了回来
Ramsey dragged him back…
回了它的窝
to her den.
是空的
It's empty.
它在哪呢
So where is she now?
你没事吧
‭You okay?
我…
I…
我觉得我已经不知道那是什么意思了
I don't think I even know what "Okay" means anymore.
马库斯
Marcus…
去宿营是我提出的
going camping was my idea.
我带他去宿营 其实我心里知道
I took him out there even though I knew.
我知道我们结束了
I knew it was over.
我喜欢马库斯
I liked Marcus.
他很温柔 贴心
He was sweet and kind.
他爱我
And he loved me.
我对他的爱远不及他对我 远不及…
More than I ever loved him. More than…
如果我告诉了他
If I'd just told him… If I…
我为什么不告诉他真话呢
Why couldn't I just tell him the truth?
- 格温 - 但我没有
- Gwen… - ‭Yeah, but I didn't.
我撒谎了
I lied.
我撒谎 好简化事情
I lied to make things easier. I…
对不起
I'm sorry. I…
我们该走了
We should go.
好
Right.
怎么了
‭What?
它来了
She's here.
没事的 保持冷静
It's okay. It's okay. Stay calm.
- 天呐 - 好吧
- Oh, my God. - ‭All right.
我们该走了
We should leave.
不不 格温 我得解决它
No, no, no, Gwen, I gotta take care of this.
否则它不会停下
It's the only way she'll stop.
待在车里
Stay in the car.
- 待在车里 - 好
- Stay in the car! - ‭Okay.
所以说你不能开车
This is why you don't drive.
那…结束了吗
So…it's over?
结束了
It's over.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯
Yeah.
狗死了 我得走了
Dog dead. Must be going.
克劳力 等等
Hey, Crowley, wait a second.
谢谢
Thank you.
他看上去挺好的
He seems nice.
是啊
Yeah.
上车吧 希望它还能跑
Let's get in. Hopefully, it still runs.
你之前说什么
Now what was that you were saying.
总先我两步的
about always being two steps ahead?
再见 克劳力
Buh-bye, Crowley.
我不是那么说的
That's not what I said.
搞什么
What the… ‭
我很高兴你尝到了一点自由的滋味
I'm glad you had a little taste of freedom.
我说的是
What I said was,
我总是先你十步
I'm always 10 steps ahead.
我说你惹我 我碾压你
I said you cross me, I crush you.
你打我
You hit me…
我用双倍力气奉还
I hit you back twice as hard.
你让我做你的狗
You make me your dog,
我让你做我的奴
I'll make you my slave.
你脖子上的铁链
That chain around your neck?
根本不算什么 时髦的装饰品而已
Was nothing. A stylish accessory.
这具皮囊
This vessel…
才是你真正的监牢
That's your true prison.
用笼子的符文和咒语做了防护
It's been warded with runes and spellwork from the Cage,
刻入了每个分子里
carved into every molecule.
在那里
‭In there?
你是我的
I own you.
我这才刚开始 所以
I'm just getting started. So…
我要把你关回你的洞里
I'm gonna put you back in your hole,
然后我要找到你的后裔
and then I'm gonna go find your spawn,
我要让你看着我把他撕成碎片
and I'm gonna rip him apart while you watch.
然后
And then?
我还是才刚开始
I'm still just getting started.
小卡 什么事
Cass, what's up?
我可能有凯莉·克莱恩的线索了
I think I have a lead on Kelly Kline.
是吗
Yeah?
她跟地狱王子大衮在一起
She's with Dagon, Prince of Hell.
好吧 我们对他有什么了解
All right, what do we know about him?
其实 是她
Actually, it's a her.
了解不多 只有些传闻和故事
And not much. It's just rumors and stories.
大衮最出名的是她疯子一般的残忍
Dagon is mostly known for her psychotic savagery.
太好了 凯莉呢
Great. So where's Kelly?
她原本在爱达荷州 科达伦
She was in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
现在 我不确定
Now? I'm not sure.
好吧 我们会把消息传出去
All right, well, we'll spread the word.
有发现告诉我们
Let us know if you find anything.
好的
Of course.
准备好了吗 兄弟
You ready, brother?
他听上去有没有怪怪的
He sound weird to you?
你的电脑又说话了吗
Is that your computer talking to you again?
（弗罗多来电）
不是
No.
是
It's,
米克·戴维斯
Mick Davies.
- 什么 - 迪恩
- What? - ‭Dean…
我没有电脑程序给我找案子
I don't have a computer program feeding me cases.
我…
I-I, uh…
格温 这两周我们所有的案子
Gwen? Every job we've worked in the last two weeks?
都来自英国记录者
They've come from the British Men of Letters.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Really? - ‭Yeah.
我没说是因为我知道你多恨他们
I didn't tell you 'cause I know how much you hate them.
不 我们恨他们 我们都恨他们
No, we hate them. Us. Together.
我知道 真的 但是
I-I get that. Yeah, I do. But … but…
迪恩 多亏米克和他的人
Dean, because of Mick and his guys,
吸血鬼始祖死了
the Alpha Vampire is dead.
他们有成果
They get results.
我也不想跟他们合作 但是
I don't like them either, but … but if …
如果我们能救人 那么
if we can save people, then it…
不管怎样 我不该瞒你
Either way, I-I shouldn't have lied to you. And…
对不起
I'm sorry, man. I-I…
好吧
Well, okay.
Okay?
我还能说什么
What do you want me to say?
我喜欢这样吗 不喜欢
Do I like it? No.
我信任他们吗 绝不
Do I trust them? Hell, no.
但你是对的
But you're right.
我们经常跟我们不信任的人合作
We work with people we don't trust all the time.
我还刚克劳力联手了呢
I mean, hell, I just Liam Neeson'd it up with Crowley.
如果你想试试看 那
So if you wanna give this a shot, then…
好吧
Fine.
但是 一旦
But the minute … and I mean the second …
我们感到不对劲 我们就撤
something feels off, we bail.
当然 没问题
Yeah. Of course. Deal.
是米克
It's Mick.
接吧
Pick it up.
我是萨姆
This is Sam.